All new students start their Bodwell experienced in boarding.
ボドウェルのすべての新入生は、寮滞在からスタートします
to improve their life skills and become independent young adults.
ライフスキルを向上させ、自立した人間になるため
Through carefully designed programming students are prepared to live more independently.
色々考えられたプログラムを用意しています
Once students demonstrate self-discipline and maturity in boarding,
学生は、寮生活で必要とされている様々なスキルを満たすと、
they are invited to apply to graduate from the boarding program
寮プログラムから、ホームステイへの移動を申請する事が可能です
for the chance to live with an english-speaking Canadian homestay family.
申請が認められると、カナダ人のホームステイ家族を案内します
In order to ensure that students are ready for home state we use many different criteria
学生が、寮からホームステイへの移動の条件を満たすためには、さまざまな基準があります
Number one: age. Students should be 16 or older.
１：年齢。学生は16歳以上でなければなりません。
Number two: Length of time in boarding
2：寮生活の期間
Students should spend at least two terms in boarding so their life skills can be properly assessed
ライフスキルを取得する為には、学生は最低2学期、寮生活をする必要があります
Number three: good academic results
3：成績
As homestay students, students will need to be more independent in their study habits
ホームステイ学生として、生活習慣だけでなく、学習習慣も身に着けていないといけません
and will not have the tutoring and study hall support that boarding offers.
ホームステイへ移動すると、寮でのStudy Timeもなくなります
We need to make sure that they can plan their study routines on their own
生徒が、自ら生活のルーティンを計画し実行できる必要があります
Number four: Behaviour. Students should not have had any disciplinary issues.
４：学校生活や寮生活で問題がないか
If they are on behavioral probation or have had recent disciplinary issues They will not be allowed to move to homestay
生徒が何かしらの処分や注意を受けている場合、ホームステイへの移動は許可されません
Number five: Life skills.
５：ライフスキル
Students should have a strong life skill score.
寮でのライフスキルの評価が高い必要があります
This score will allow us to measure student's readiness for independent living
このスコアは、生徒が自立した生活ができるための評価対象となります
The score is shown on the boarding report card that is received by parents regularly.
このスコアは、保護者へも定期的に寮レポートして配られます
Once all of these factors are considered
これらすべての要因が考慮し
Students will either be accepted or rejected in their request to leave boarding
学生が、寮からホームステイへ移動が認められるかがきまり
and move to a Bodwell homestay.
Bodwellのホームステイに移動します。
It is important to remember that for safety reasons,
ホームステイへの移動は、
homestay is a privilege that is earned. Only those that have truly mastered the ability to be independent,
自立した生徒のみに与えられる特権です
both in their life skills and in their study habits, will be successful in a homestay.
ライフスキルと学習習慣の両方において、充分問題ない生徒が
Through our experience we want to ensure that all students that go to homestay continue to be successful at Bodwell
ホームステイでも成功します。その為、ボドウェルではこの様なプロセスがあります